Hello, welcome to this episode of Learn German in Hindi.
As we
decided last time,
what we are going to do today is Nominee and
Registrar Dr. Because today we are going to
take a test on 25 passages on this, so I hope
that you guys must have revised it before, if
not then
revise it first and then give the test, it will be a little hard
and we will
take the test in the same pattern as we have learnt,
how did we learn, first we learnt what is
novelty and what is attract,
after that we learnt Dayal Das for Joe,
after that we learnt how to use mirror mirror,
then we learnt mine thei, after that actress
position is okay and then we solved complex
sentence, we are going to do the test in the same way, so let's
start, now you will
see 25 questions on the screen, as
I always say, without any cheating,
solve them properly, you can scan and
pause here, this question will be finished,
then you can take out this portion
and one small thing is fun, you know that
I have deliberately used the word team simple here
which you used, first and
tow ball zone motor farmtrac tractor
so that it becomes easy for you that you know
its male-female laddu, once you
understand how to operate it, then you can
do it for the rest of the male-female networks as well,
so okay solve it now, after searching by singing, you
can go ahead now,
I hope that all of you must have solved it properly, it must have been a
little lost, it was a
bit simple, we will see that later, now
before seeing the answer, what I want to tell you is that
if you remember what you did, you did it
step by step, if you do
not follow it then it will be a mistake, in this
previous one, if you are new, if you remember we had
seen that there are subjects, there are objects, these
directors are with minutes, then
how to do admin, then which table to see for the and
for if if i is there then
whose replacement is there, if you are there then with whom do you have to
repeat, we all this  If you do
n't watch for questions, then that video will be over.
If there is something different, I will explain it. So, I will
explain directly in this video.
If you have any doubts, you
can go and watch the first video. If
you get any doubts from that too, what can you do? You
can post in the comments below. I will
try to answer it. So, let's
start in that. Let's see the answer.
In the beginning, it's very simple. Like we started with
the white thing,
Reddy and restraint. I love push. That's why
Dadasa to opposite it is pledged with the whole
school
medium. We will talk about hair removal.
This is what she is. This hug.
Next, from 9 newsroom, less distribution ka ishq
upma mitaai ne mau 245. Let's mix it with
Mike and this black
human to issue of
colors. Just something. So,
if it's black, it's fine. Otherwise, don't do it.
Okay, the young man has a
rule that that thing has been looted. Loot
blouse do. This will be confusion in this city.
If you go directly and do it step by
step, then there will never be any confusion.
Illegal work brown  ne them dhar auto this
provision key
place with the recent years paste minute
signin jo dev
love affair
believe
virveer comes
with government v
mid-range mou to do i love you watch this week
responsibility va that loves his father
died in the latter
vighna
more 1968 to pig ko utterly simple wala thoda sa
use karne tak aapko 15
se tension aaya ho to aaye people with tamil
see what is anil proper noun hai so
speed limit anil hi karna laga das nothing will seem
clear now let's get into prepositions
come come without myka
ishq makun manav tokyo hona is registrar
come for my father is this last month
fighter again then what time is that come after his
mother egg com named banner motor
why because nose do hai we go to our
number ghaghra kunjar james john this
dip dip has and obscene prepositions see
i govinda restaurant is wheat in das
restaurant place changed i the
restaurant style in this restaurant was
in the same place if you only  If you
remember the question cut then my mother loves my daughter let's try it a little
in both the places also so
it is simple because for female there is
update in this time so minor voter
list - Dr. Same is a little more hard now they
say that father please with Jason data in
fast appeal minute white why dip both
and in acting most people have a question
my father gives my son my friend
away from you who is the doer father has done the deed
and who is the indirect object
with what will happen mind water gift my
name zone - institute a reminder
how many different ways it went I hope you
all have checked your answers
whatever your answer is you can put it in the comments
see it is possible that you might have
lost a little bit that if you have
not practiced 5 sentences everyday then you will get a
little lost if you do not remember some concept then go and
watch the videos again and if
this is a trick then you keep practicing a lot if you
still have some give up from any party then
you can ask in the comments  I
hope you liked today's video.
Next Sunday in the next episode we will
test all of you on the past tense
of German, so till then study it
friends, very important part,
we will meet next Sunday.
Thanks.